http://www.queenzone.com/privacy-policy.aspx

Privacy Policy
HomeBandFreddie MercuryAdd your own Freddie Mercury tributeBrian MayJohn DeaconRoger TaylorTalkBlogsChatForumsQueen FansQueen Fan ChartInformationArticlesBiographyDiscographyFAQNews ArchiveRare QueenLinksMediaDownloadsPicture GalleryQuizQueen Trivia QuizQueen Lyrics GameQueen Picture PuzzleScreen SaversStage of ChampionsVideoMembersJoinMember SurveyFavorite Queen Band MemberFavorite Queen AlbumProfileYour blogsSite settingsAdd to QueenzoneAdd feature articlesAdd FAQAdd newsAdd picturesAdd a song to the Stage of ChampionsAdd
QuotesYour EmailLog outAboutAbout Community Recognition Contact usDonatePrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We take your privacy seriously! We will not provide any of your details to any other entity.
This is the web site of QueenZone.com. Operated in part by Richard Orchard, it is "owned" by the collective of Queen fans that make it a home.
Our postal address
is 3 Mottram Place Morley WA 6062, Australia. We can be reached via e-mail at queen@thinkingwebsites.com.au.
For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server
automatically recognizes only the consumer's domain name and IP address, but not the e-mail address. We collect some other information of those who post messages to our
bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail,
the e-mail addresses of those who make postings to our chat areas, aggregate information
on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer,
such as survey information and/or site registrations.
The information we collect
is used for internal review and is then discarded, used to improve the content of
our Web page, used to customize the content and/or layout of our page for each individual
visitor, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site.
With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences,
customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information
that the visitor sends.
If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future,
please let us know by or adjust your options in your profile..
With respect to
Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships
with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of
your visit to our site, ad server companies may collect information such as your
domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. For further information,
consult the privacy policies of: Google.
From time to time, we may use customer information
for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our
information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy
changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the
ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information
is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically.
Users can have this information corrected by or modifying
their profile.
With respect to security: We have appropriate security measures in
place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website.
These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address,
or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide
advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more
information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information
used by these companies, click here.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site.
Google's
use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based
on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt
out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the
Google ad and content network
privacy policy
.
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us on the details above.
